027 5171559 jeremy.jonas@hotmail.co.nz https://jeremyjonas.dev 16 Harris Dr, Silverdale

D 1		O 1	
Personal	Pro	11	
1 CISUIIAI	1110	ш	ľ

I am an enthusiastic new web developer with a background in both retail and the real estate industry. With 8 years of experience in the retail industry and two in the real estate industry I pride myself in my communication and teamwork skills. I am passionate about learning and technology which is why I made the switch to becoming a web developer. I have a strong interest in electronics and 3D printing so when I am not coding, I will usually be designing and 3D printing something or finding new and interesting ways to combine code and electronics to push an Arduino to the limits.

## Key Skills and Attributes

### Communication

I have developed communication skills mostly during my time in the retail industry where it was essential to be able to communicate with people from all backgrounds and at times find ways to overcome language barriers.

### **Technology**

I am always keeping up to date with the latest technology surrounding computers, electronics and now 3D printing. I have amassed a huge knowledge in the electronics field, starting from a very young age, and computers soon became a passion for me.

### Organisational and planning skills

During my time in the real estate industry I was responsible for coordinating teams across 3 offices, planning standard operating procedures and producing instructional materials for the teams.

## **Coaching and training others**

Also during my time in the real estate industry, I was responsible for training new team members and coaching the existing team when new processes were introduced.

### **Customer Service**

The first several years of my working life were working on the shop floor helping customers and other staff. I have sound customer service techniques and the ability to deal with difficult customers in an appropriate way without reacting.

027 5171559 jeremy.jonas@hotmail.co.nz https://jeremyjonas.dev 16 Harris Dr, Silverdale

Experience

# **Enspiral Dev Academy**

October 2018 - December 2018

Newmarket, Auckland

Position: Graduate - Full Stack JavaScript Developer

During late 2018 I completed a 9-week intensive coding bootcamp at EDA where I worked as part of a team to learn full stack JavaScript along with a range of sub technologies. The bootcamp was geared towards teaching us how to learn new technologies while also teaching us enough JavaScript to make professional and full feature websites and web apps. My cohort and I spent around 900 hours learning and coding and produced projects both individually and as a team. During one of our team projects I took on the task of adding a life filter search function to the app, along with assistance from one of my tutors I was able to get the live filter search working with Redux on a React based webpage.

The project is available at https://github.com/kowhai-2018/fishlist

#### **Glovers Real Estate**

September 2016 - October 2018

Green Bay, New Lynn and Titirangi, Auckland

Position: Administration Team Leader

**Duties include:** 

- Overseeing 3 teams of office administrators.
- Creating new standard operating procedures and instructional materials.
- Training/onboarding new team members and coaching existing team members.
- Providing technical support to the teams of real estate agents.

### Personal Achievements in the Role

While at Glovers I was part of a team of two who ran the process of changing the company over to a new software system which involved hundreds of hours of planning, testing, and debugging to create new processes for every single existing process within the company. My team was responsible for the training of every single staff member within the company on the new processes and features specific to their job, as well as taking feedback and bug reports to produce fixes and updates processes.

## The Warehouse Limited

August 2013 - July 2016

Lyall Bay, Wellington

Position: Sales/Technology Specialist

Duties included:

- Using sales techniques to help customers select the product that best suited their technology related needs.
- Providing technical help and setup advice to customers who had purchased technology products.
- Using effective communication skills with speakers of other languages.

027 5171559

jeremy.jonas@hotmail.co.nz https://jeremyjonas.dev

16 Harris Dr, Silverdale

- Attending regular meetings with the Assistant Store Manager to track how department sales were progressing and working on any actions required as a result of sales performance.
- Providing support to customers (over the phone and via email) with tech product questions.

## **Geeks on Wheels HQ**

August – September 2015

Tacy Street, Kilbirnie, Wellington Position: Workshop Technician

During August 2015, I completed one month of full-time work experience at Geeks on Wheels as a workshop technician. While there, I gained a huge amount of knowledge and support from the staff, including hands on "real world" workshop situations. This included diagnosing and finding fixes for PC faults, and testing the fixes. I also spent some time building PCs from scratch and replacing hardware in existing PCs.

### The Warehouse Limited

March 2010-January 2012

New Plymouth

Position: Stockroom Team Member

**Duties included:** 

- Unloading stock on pallets from trucks daily.
- Daily scanning and entering of high-risk stock into the database daily following its delivery.
- Sorting stock into pallets to support the night fill team.
- Housekeeping to keep the area clean.
- Daily data entries into the database.
- General administrative work relating to the stockroom.

### **Malcove Distributers**

March 2010-January 2012

Auckland and New Plymouth

Position: Contractor/ Bike Mechanic

Duties included:

- Assembling boxed bikes on behalf of customers.
- Providing advice and maintenance tips to customers.
- Diagnosing faults reported by customers and carrying out appropriate repairs.
- Being a contact between Malcove and The Warehouse store where I was contracting.

027 5171559 jeremy.jonas@hotmail.co.nz https://jeremyjonas.dev 16 Harris Dr, Silverdale

## **Education and Training**

# **Computer Power Plus - Wellington**

2014-2015

Diploma in Systems Technology (Level 5)

## Spotswood College - New Plymouth

2003-2007

NCEA Level 3 with University Entrance

### Hobbies

- Computers, including computer programs and hardware.
- Electronics, including microprocessors and circuit design.
  See <a href="https://github.com/Jeremy-Jonas/door-lock">https://github.com/Jeremy-Jonas/door-lock</a> for an electronic lock project I recently completed which used electronics, coding and 3D printing to create.
- 3D printing, including 3D design and part modelling.

#### Referees

- Bryce Kehoe Teacher, Enspiral Dev Academy
- Sam Bellairs Owner & Director, Glovers Real Estate

Contact Information available upon request.